(Leonard:)Hey.
Wanna get a little crazy?
(Leonard:)What are you thinking?
(Penny:)Let's slide over to Sheldon's spot
and make out.
(Leonard:)You are a dirty girl.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Penny(as the making out is interrupted by a knock on the door):)Oh, God, how did he know?
Hello?
(Leonard:)-Hi, Howard.
PENNY: Heh.
(Howard:)Am I interrupting?
(Leonard:)Little bit, yeah.
Guess I should've called.
(Penny:)Yeah, maybe.
[SIGHS]
[CLICKING TONGUE]
(Howard:)Tonight's the night I usually go
line dancing with Raj at the Palomino.
(Leonard:)Uh-huh.
(Howard:)But he's working with Sheldon.
(Penny:)-Yes. We know.
HOWARD: Hoo.
(Howard:)Want me to leave?
(Leonard:)You know, whatever.
(Howard:)I guess I can hang for a little while.
(Howard:)So, what are we watching?
Sex and the City, yikes.